<resources>
    <string name="app_name">5 ways to make eggs</string>
    <string name="hardBoiled">1) Hard boiled eggs</string>
    <string name="hardBoiled_steps">Place your <b>eggs</b> in a pot and cover with cold water by 1 inch. Bring to a <b>boil</b> over medium-high heat, then cover, remove from the heat and set aside 8 to 10 minutes. Drain, cool in ice water and peel.</string>
    <string name="fried">2) Fried eggs</string>
    <string name="fried_steps"><b>1</b>. For Over-Easy or Over-Hard Eggs: HEAT 2 tsp. butter in nonstick skillet over medium-high heat until hot.\n\n<b>2</b>. BREAK eggs and SLIP into pan, 1 at a time. IMMEDIATELY reduce heat to low.\n\n<b>3</b>. COOK SLOWLY until whites are completely set and yolks begin to thicken but are not hard.</string>
    <string name="poached">3) Poached eggs</string>
    <string name="poached_steps"><b>1</b>. Pour cold water into a large saucepan until 8cm deep. Add vinegar. Bring to the boil over medium heat. Reduce heat to low (water should still be simmering around the edge).\n\n<b>2</b>. Crack 1 egg into a shallow bowl. Using a wooden spoon, stir water to create a whirlpool. Tip egg into water. Cook for 2 to 3 minutes for a soft yolk or 3 to 4 minutes for firm. Using a slotted spoon, remove egg from water. \n\n<b>3</b>. Skim foam from water. Poach remaining eggs. Serve eggs on toast.</string>
    <string name="scrambled">4) Scrambled eggs</string>
    <string name="scrambled_steps"><b>1</b>. BEAT eggs, milk, salt and pepper in bowl until blended.\n\n<b>2</b>. HEAT butter in large nonstick skillet over medium heat until hot. POUR IN egg mixture. \n\n<b>3</b>. As eggs begin to set, GENTLY PULL the eggs across the pan with an inverted turner, forming large soft curds. CONTINUE cooking – pulling, lifting and folding eggs – until thickened and no visible liquid egg remains. Do not stir constantly. REMOVE from heat. SERVE immediately.</string>
    <string name="omelet">5) Omelet</string>
    <string name="omelet_steps"><b>1</b>. BEAT eggs, water, salt and pepper in small bowl until blended.\n\n<b>2</b>. HEAT butter in 7 to 10-inch nonstick omelet pan or skillet over medium-high heat until hot. TILT pan to coat bottom. POUR IN egg mixture. Mixture should set immediately at edges.\n\n<b>3</b>. GENTLY PUSH cooked portions from edges toward the center with inverted turner so that uncooked eggs can reach the hot pan surface. CONTINUE cooking, tilting pan and gently moving cooked portions as needed.\n\n<b>4</b>.When top surface of eggs is thickened and no visible liquid egg remains, PLACE filling on one side of the omelet. FOLD omelet in half with turner. With a quick flip of the wrist, turn pan and INVERT or SLIDE omelet onto plate. SERVE immediately.</string>
    <string name="continue_"><b>SWIPE TO CONTINUE --></b></string>
    <string name="ended"><b>THE END</b></string>
</resources>
